dupont.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy | DuPont USA

We've noticed you're using a version of Internet Explorer that is out of date and may not support all the features on our website. For a better browsing experience, we suggest upgrading to a newer version of [Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/download-ie "Follow link").

  *     * About Us
      * Our Approach

####  Our  Approach  

The DuPont approach to solving global challenges is rooted in our science and engineering expertise.

        * #### > Global Challenges

Our expertise and global reach help promote safety and health for the planet and its inhabitants.

        * #### > Strategic Priorities

Our focus revolves around Agriculture & Nutrition, Advanced Materials and Bio-Based Industrials.

        * #### > Innovation Delivery

We create a bridge from need to market with expert insights, peerless science and technical skills.

        * #### > Perspectives

Learn about our businesses, products and unique approach to solving global challenges.

      * Our Company

####  Our  Company  

See what makes DuPont one of the most successful science and engineering companies in the world.

        * #### > Values

Our core values govern our internal business practices and partnerships, and guide our innovations.

        * #### > Leadership

Meet our Chair and CEO, board of directors, corporate executives, and regional and functional leaders.

        * #### > Businesses 

We develop innovative, practical solutions that address the challenges of our changing world.

        * #### > History

For more than two centuries, DuPont has delivered innovative solutions to tackle global challenges.

        * #### > Awards & Recognition

Our company and its employees make a difference in their communities and beyond.

        * #### > Locations

Find DuPont offices and sites around the world.

      * Sustainability

####  Sustainability  

DuPont creates solutions for safe, sufficient crops; renewable energy; and protection for the planet.

        * #### > Sustainability Commitments

We work closely with partners to improve our global operations, and uphold our purpose and values.

        * #### > Outreach

We support communities where we live and work, and help improve quality of life through STEM education.

        * #### > Leading with Innovation

Our world-class, innovative approach provides solutions for some of the world's biggest challenges.

      *     * Product Lines
      * Agricultural Products

        * #### > Animal Nutrition & Disease Prevention

DuPont is helping to meet increased global demand for affordable meat products with optimized in-feed animal nutrition and...

        * #### > Crop Protection

DuPont Crop Protection uses inclusive thinking to create answers in insect, weed and disease control that help growers...

        * #### > Seed

Growing success with Pioneer® brand agricultural seeds. Proven performance and plenty of options – that's what our product...

      * Food & Personal Care

        * #### > Dietary Supplement Ingredients

Dietary supplement ingredients with clinically documented, health-enhancing effects.

        * #### > Food Ingredients

DuPont brings together a wide range of sustainable food ingredients to increase the quality of food products, while...

        * #### > Food Protection

DuPont offers a broad range of food protection products to help you meet the rigorous standards of your food safety programs...

        * #### > Personal Care 

From skin care to hair care, DuPont Personal Care products are designed to serve a variety of your needs.

      * High Performance Materials

        * #### > Construction Materials

Includes brands like: Corian® solid surface, Elvaloy® resins, Sorona® flooring, Tyvek® weather barriers, and Zodiaq® quartz...

        * #### > Display & Lighting Materials

DuPont offers innovative solutions to improve performance while reducing the manufacturing cost of LED lighting and displays.

        * #### > Electronic & Electrical Materials

DuPont offers the industry’s broadest array of high performance electronic and electrical materials.

        * #### > Industrial Films

DuPont offers materials with unique properties that withstand extreme temperatures and other demanding environments.

        * #### > Materials for Sporting Goods Industry

The demands of the sporting goods industry require the use of consistent, high performing yet cost effective materials....

        * #### > Packaging Materials & Solutions

DuPont experts work with customers to create specialized, cost-effective packaging solutions that deliver high performance...

        * #### > Printing & Package Printing

DuPont offers high quality, productivity and sustainable solutions for the printing and package printing industry.

        * #### > Solar / Photovoltaic Materials

For over 40 years our innovations in PV materials have led the photovoltaics industry forward. 

      * Industrial Biotechnology

        * #### > Advanced Biofuels

DuPont is committed to reducing dependence on fossil fuels with cost-effective manufacturing of cellulosic ethanol and other...

        * #### > Industrial Enzymes & Other Bioactives

DuPont develops biobased solutions using enzymes, microbes, and other bioactives to help improve the performance and...

      * People & Process Safety

        * #### > Clean Technologies

        * #### > Consulting Services – Sustainable Solutions

Discover how our sustainable business consultants customize solutions based on DuPont best practices to help clients improve...

        * #### > Personal Protective Equipment

Learn more about Kevlar® fiber for ballistic and cut protection, Nomex® fiber for flame hazards, and Tyvek® and Tychem®...

      * Polymers & Fibers

        * #### > Additives & Modifiers

We help our customers cost-effectively overcome their challenges with our range of additives and modifiers for polymers.

        * #### > Fabrics, Fibers & Non-Wovens

Learn more about Kevlar® aramid fiber for cut and ballistic protection, Nomex® fiber for heat and flame hazards, and Tyvek®...

        * #### > Plastics, Polymers & Resins

DuPont collaborates with customers around the world, providing a spectrum of polymer materials and expert application...

      *     * Industries Served
      *         * ####  > Agriculture

#### Agriculture

DuPont Agriculture offerings deliver global nutrition through higher crop yields and healthier foods while developing solutions to help meet the world's energy needs.

        * ####  > Automotive

#### Automotive

See how our broad family of materials and global development experts can help the automotive industry reduce emissions and improve fuel economy, design, safety, and affordability.

        * ####  > Building & Construction

#### Building & Construction

At DuPont, we're focused on dynamic science that generates real-world solutions. That's why DuPont is at the forefront of building science, with brands you depend on, like Tyvek®, SentryGlas®, Corian® solid surfaces, Zodiaq® quartz surfaces and Kevlar®.

        * ####  > Electronics

#### Electronics

With a deep understanding of materials science, a commitment to technology leadership, a wide range of process expertise and a long history of innovation, DuPont offers the industry’s broadest array of high performance electronic materials.

        * ####  > Energy

#### Energy

With the world’s population projected to surpass 9 billion by 2050, now is the time to prepare for a secure energy future. We invite you to collaborate with our global teams to find science-driven, sustainable energy solutions. 

        * ####  > Food & Beverage

#### Food & Beverage

At DuPont, we're putting science to work in the food and beverage industry — improving the nutritional value of food, ensuring food safety, and finding smart, sustainable solutions to feed a growing population.

        * ####  > Government & Public Sector

#### Government & Public Sector

DuPont Government & Public Sector solutions address the unique requirements of federal, state and local government agencies—particularly in the areas of life protection and emergency response.

        * ####  > Health Care & Medical

#### Health Care & Medical

DuPont offers a broad range of healthcare products and high-performance materials that help create safer healthcare environments, contribute to innovations in medical devices and help protect the health of patients and healthcare providers worldwide.

        * ####  > Marine

#### Marine

DuPont brings science-powered technologies, products and services to the marine industry that facilitate regulatory compliance enhance performance and promote safety.

        * ####  > Mining

#### Mining

Dupont Mining products and services help improve extraction, personal protection, safety and more. Processing and transporting of highly abrasive and corrosive, bitumen, slurry and tailings require the innovation and technology that DuPont can provide.

        * ####  > Packaging & Printing

#### Packaging & Printing

DuPont provides end-to-end technical expertise and a wide range of cost-effective materials to help create packaging innovations that support partners' branding, performance, and sustainability goals.

        * ####  > Plastics

#### Plastics

Today you need more from your suppliers than just materials. You need a resource that can carry a project from concept to commercialization. DuPont Performance Polymers can be that partner.

        * ####  > Safety & Protection

#### Safety & Protection

In the face of growing global industrialization, DuPont takes safety and protection seriously. Learn how DuPont continues to improve upon its materials and workplace safety performance to help keep all of us safe in the toughest conditions.

      * #### Industries Served

Learn about the many industries that DuPont serves in the United States.

  * 

rev. August 18, 2016

E. I. du Pont de Nemours and Company* and its affiliates  (“DuPont”) are concerned about privacy issues and want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information.  Together with DuPont’s [Global Information Privacy Policy](http://www2.dupont.com/Privacy/en_US/global_policy_english.html), this Privacy Statement describes DuPont practices in connection with information that we collect through the website or mobile application owned and controlled by DuPont from which you are accessing this Privacy Statement (respectively, the “Site” and the “App”), as well as offline where notice is legally required.  By providing Personal Information to DuPont, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement. 

If you apply for a job through the Site, DuPont use of the Personal Information you provide through the Career Center is governed by a separate privacy notice, not this Privacy Statement.  Please click [here](https://dupontimpl.taleo.net/careersection/application.jss?lang=en&type=1&csNo=10161&portal=16240470091&reqNo=384562) to review DuPont privacy Applicant Privacy Notice for job seekers who apply for jobs through the Site.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Personal Information DuPont Collects  

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual, such as:

  * Name;
  * Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses);
  * Telephone or fax number;
  * Email address;
  * Credit and debit card number;
  * Vendor Tax ID numbers;
  * National ID numbers such as Social Security Numbers;
  * Financial information when you apply for credit;
  * Purchase history.

DuPont collects Personal Information when you participate in various opportunities that we provide, for example:

  * When you order a product or service or make a request.
  * When you register your purchase of a DuPont product.
  * When you submit a warranty card.
  * When you register for subscriptions, technology forum or other communications through the Site or App.
  * When you participate in a contest, promotion, sweepstakes, survey or other promotion.
  * When you participate in a blog or forum.
  * When we conduct market research, meet you at a trade show or other event.

We may combine Personal Information that we collect about you with Personal Information you provide to DuPont through other sources, such as product registrations, inquiries or marketing events.  We will use the combined Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Statement for as long as it is combined.

## How We Use Personal Information  

We may use Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * Respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you e-mail alerts.
  * Send you important information regarding the Site or App, changes to DuPont’s terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information. 
  * Complete and fulfill your purchase, for example, to process your payments, have your order delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service.
  * Send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, including information about trade shows.
  * Personalize your experience on the Site by presenting products and offers tailored to you.
  * Allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities.  Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that read these rules carefully.
  * Permit you to send messages to a friend through the Site or App.  By using this functionality, you are telling DuPont that you are entitled to use and provide DuPont with your friend’s name and email address. 
  * Allow you to communicate and interact with others through the Site or App (for example, through a blog, message board, messaging functionality, chat functionality, profile or other social media).
  * Permit you to register and participate in technology forums and other events with DuPont.
  * Enable DuPont business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, researching and developing new products, enhancing DuPont’s website, improving DuPont’s services, developing marketing events, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of DuPont’s promotional campaigns. 
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce DuPont terms and conditions; (e) to protect DuPont operations; (f) to protect DuPont rights, privacy, safety or property, you or others; and (g) to allow DuPont to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

## How Personal Information is Disclosed  

  * Your Personal Information may be disclosed:
  * Within the [DuPont Group of Companies](http://www.dupont.com/subsidiaries.html) for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement.  E.I. du Pont de Nemours and Company* and the local affiliate with whom you are interacting are jointly responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information.
  * To DuPont’s third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, product distribution, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, email delivery services, credit card processing, auditing services and other similar services to enable them to provide services.
  * To third parties such as agents and distributers to facilitate the sale and distribution of DuPont products and services which may include marketing communications.
  * To third parties sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
  * To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Site.
  * To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of DuPont business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce DuPont terms and conditions; (e) to protect DuPont operations; (f) to protect DuPont rights, privacy, safety or property, you or others; and (g) to allow DuPont to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
  * By you, when you participate in features on a DuPont Site or App that provide the opportunity to interact with DuPont and others (for example a blog, message board, messaging functionality, chat functionality, profile or other social media).  When you use these features you should be aware that any information you submit, including your name, location and e-mail address, may be publicly available to others. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit through these features and we strongly discourage you from disclosing any sensitive Personal Information (such as health or credit card information) through these features.  If you use these features, your Personal Information may remain on the Site or App even after you cease use of the Site or App.

## NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Non-Personal Information We Collect

“Non-Personal Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity, such as:

  * Browser information;
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies;
  * Demographic information and other information provided by you;
  * Aggregated information.

### How We Collect Non-Personal Information

DuPont and DuPont’s third party service providers may collect Non-Personal Information in a variety of ways, including:

  * Through your browser:  Certain information is collected by most browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version.
  * Using cookies:  Cookies allow a web server to transfer data to a computer for recordkeeping and other purposes.  We use cookies and other technologies to, among other things, better serve you with more tailored information, to facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Site, and to provide you with personalized marketing.  If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies.  Some features of the Site may not work properly if you decline the use of cookies.  To learn more about cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
  * Using pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs or other similar technologies:  These may be used in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted email messages to, among other things, track the actions of Site users and email recipients, measure the success of DuPont marketing campaigns and compile statistics about Site usage and response rates. 
  * From you:  Information such as your location, as well as other information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information.  Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Site or App.
  * By aggregating information:  Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Site or App, (for example, we may use Personal Information to calculate the percentage of DuPont users who have a particular telephone area code).

## How We Use and Disclose Non-Personal Information

Because Non-Personal Information does not personally identify you, we may use and disclose Non-Personal Information for any purpose.  In some instances, we may combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location).  
If we combine any Non-Personal Information with Personal Information, e.g., when we combine information you provide upon registration with Non-Personal Information to provide you with targeted personalized marketing, the combined information will be treated by DuPont as Personal Information. 

## IP ADDRESSES

Your “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP).

## How We Collect IP Addresses

An IP Address is identified and logged automatically in DuPont server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited.  Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many web sites.

## How DuPont Uses and Discloses IP Addresses?  

DuPont uses IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, administering the Site and presenting content that is tailored to your country.  We may also use and disclose IP Addresses for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information.  Please note that we treat IP Addresses, server log files and related information as Non-Personal Information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law.

## INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING  

DuPont and DuPont third party service providers use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs or similar technologies to track the actions of Site users and email recipients across non-affiliate websites over time, in order to personalize your experience on the Site by presenting advertisements that are more relevant to you.  For example, we use third party service providers, to present products and offers tailored to the preferences and interests demonstrated by your online activity over time.

## THIRD PARTY SITES

This Privacy Statement does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site to which the Site or the App contains a link.  The inclusion of a link on the Site or the App does not imply endorsement of the linked site by DuPont.

## THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS  

DuPont may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit a DuPont Site.  Please note that these companies may use information about your visit to this Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

## SECURITY  

DuPont uses reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information under DuPont control.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with DuPont is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with DuPont has been compromised), please immediately notify DuPont of the problem by contacting DuPont in accordance with the “Contacting DuPont” section below.

## CHOICES AND ACCESS

### Your choices regarding DuPont’s use and disclosure of your Personal Information  

DuPont gives you many choices regarding DuPont’s use and disclosure of your Personal Information for marketing purposes.  By contacting the [DuPont Inquiry Management Center](http://www2.dupont.com/Contact/en_US/corp/Privacy/PrivacyRequest.html?lang=ENG), you may opt-out from receiving future electronic marketing messages from DuPont and request that we not share your Personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes.

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your Personal Information from the databases of unaffiliated third parties with which DuPont has already shared your Personal Information (i.e., to which we have already provided your Personal Information as of the date that we implement your opt-out request).  Please also note that if you do opt-out of receiving marketing-related messages from DuPont, we may still send you important administrative messages, and you cannot opt-out from receiving administrative messages.

### How you can access, change or suppress your Personal Information  

If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, delete or otherwise limit DuPont use of your Personal Information that has been previously provided to DuPont, you may contact the [DuPont Inquiry Management Center](http://www2.dupont.com/Contact/en_US/corp/Privacy/PrivacyRequest.html?lang=ENG).

In your request, please make clear what information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from a DuPont database or otherwise let DuPont know what limitations you would like to put on DuPont use of your Personal Information.  We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

## RETENTION PERIOD

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

## USE OF SITE BY CHILDREN

DuPont is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities.  DuPont does not target the Site or the App to children less than fourteen (14) years of age or knowingly collect information from children for the purpose of selling products or services.  DuPont does participate in select educational programs such as science and environmental awareness in support of schools and communities.

## CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or where we have engaged a service provider, and by using DuPont Site or App you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including to the United States, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.

## SENSITIVE INFORMATION

We ask that you not send DuPont, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Site or App or otherwise to DuPont.

## UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

We may change this Privacy Statement.  Please take a look at the “LAST UPDATED” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Statement was last revised.  Any changes to this Privacy Statement will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Statement on the Site or App.  Your use of the Site or App following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Statement.

## CONTACTING DUPONT  

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact DuPont at [DuPont Inquiry Management Center](http://www2.dupont.com/Contact/en_US/corp/Privacy/PrivacyRequest.html?lang=ENG), or please write to the following address:

**DuPont Inquiry Management Center**

Chestnut Run Plaza 735  
974 Centre Road  
Wilmington, DE 19805    
Toll-free: 855-569-0964  
E-mail: Privacy-Office@dupont.com
